[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":117386,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":134093,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure t hat when  we combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":10254,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":144349,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":8263,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":152613,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":1863,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":154478,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":3519,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":157998,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1376,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":159375,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the seco nd one t o it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":4919,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":164295,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1519,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":165815,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":4096,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":169912,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1431,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":171344,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":2704,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":174049,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub >6</sub>  0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1199,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":175249,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":3023,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":178273,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1199,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":179473,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br  /><br />  (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":3559,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":183033,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1126,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":184161,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your re sult.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":2456,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":186618,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1111,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":187730,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":3376,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":191107,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1343,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":192451,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":4447,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":196899,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":991,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":197891,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":46813,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":244706,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inv erse und er +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":130702,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":375410,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":10848,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":386261,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1927,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":388188,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br  /><br / > (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":6008,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":394197,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1295,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":395493,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":3816,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":399311,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1102,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":400413,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":2392,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":402806,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity und er +<sub >6</sub>.","rt":1232,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":404039,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":2847,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":406886,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":992,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":407880,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simp ly be pe rformed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":95119,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":503000,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</su b> 2, bu t there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":64998,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":567999,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":7312,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":575312,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":1302,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":576615,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br / > (Remem ber, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":3009,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":579625,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":23056,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":602682,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub >? <br / ><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":6331,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":609015,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":2987,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":612004,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":7984,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":619989,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":2207,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":622197,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question wit h feedba ck to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":10947,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":633144,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":3936,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":637081,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1094,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":638176,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":4303,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":642480,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":4024,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":646505,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":3127,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":649633,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":2575,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":652209,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":6136,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":658346,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"On the following question, and several others later in the HIT, we will ask you to explain how you got your answer. On these questions, you will be given one box for your answer to the question, and a second for your explanation. Please explain your thought process in as much detail as possible (at least one sentence, and more if you can).","rt":9521,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":667868,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":" What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":true,"explanation":"add 4 plus 1 equals 5, answer is 5 since it is smaller than 9","explanation_history":["add 4 plus 1 equals f","add 4 plus 1 equals 5, anc","add 4 plus 1 equals 5, answer is 5 since it is smaller than 9"],"response_history":["5"],"rt":36051,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":703920,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":true,"explanation":"add 8 and 4 equals 12, subtract 9 since answer is greater than 9, equals 3 ","explanation_history":["add 8 and 4, an","add 8 and 4, a","add 8 and 4, subtract 9 ","add 8 and 4 , subtract 9 ","add 8 and 4 e, subtract 9 ","add 8 and 4 eq, su btract 9  ","add 8 and 4 equ, subtract 9 ","add 8 and 4 equa, subtract 9 ","add 8 and 4 equal, subtract 9 ","add 8 and 4 equals, subtract 9 ","add 8 and 4 equals , subtract 9 ","add 8 and 4 equals 12, subtract 9  ","add 8 and 4 equals 12, subtract 9 s ","add 8 and 4 equals 12, subtract 9 sin ","add 8 and 4 equals 12, subtract 9 sinc ","add 8 and 4 equals 12, subtract 9 since  ","add 8 and 4 equals 12, subtract 9 since a ","add 8 and 4 equals 12, subtract 9 since an ","add 8 and 4 equals 12, subtract 9 since ans ","add 8 and 4 equals 12, subtract 9 since answe ","add 8 and 4 equals 12, subtract 9 since answer  ","add 8 and 4 equals 12, subtract 9 since answer i ","add 8 and 4 equals 12, subtract 9 since answer is  ","add 8 and 4 equals 12, subtract 9 since answer is l ","add 8 and 4 equals 12, subtract 9 since answer is  ","add 8 and 4 equals 12, subtract 9 since answer is g ","add 8 and 4 equals 12, subtract 9 since answer is gr ","add 8 and 4 equals 12, subtract 9 since answer is gr e ","add  8 and 4 equals 12, subtract 9 since answer is grea ","add 8 and 4 equals 12, subtract 9 since answer is great ","add 8 and 4 equals 12, subtract 9 since answer is greater  ","add 8 and 4 equals 12, subtract 9 since answer is greater th ","add 8 and 4 equals 12, subtract 9 since answer is greater tha ","add 8 and 4 equals 12, subtract 9 since answer is greater than  ","add 8 and 4 equals 12, subtract 9 since answer is greater than 9 ","add 8 and 4 equals 12, subtract 9 since answer is greater than 9,  ","add 8 and 4 equals 12, subtract 9 since answer is greater than 9, e ","add 8 and 4 equals 12, subtract 9 since answer is greater than 9, eq ","add 8 and 4 equals 12, subtract 9 since answer is greater than 9, equ ","add 8 and 4 equals 12, subtract 9 since answer is greater than 9, equa ","add 8 and 4 equals 12, subtract 9 since answer is greater than 9, equal ","add 8 and 4 equals 12, subtract 9 since answer is greater than 9, equals  ","add 8 and 4 equals 12, subtract 9 sin ce answe r is greater than 9, equals 3 "],"response_history":["3"],"rt":43355,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":747277,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":true,"explanation":"identity is 0 because when you add it to another number, you always get that identical number (9+0=9)","explanation_history":["identity is 0 because when you add it to n","identity is 0 because when you add it to another number, you always get that identical number (9=","identity is 0 because when you add it to another number, you always get that identical number (9+0=0","identity is 0 because when you add it to another number, you always get that identical number (9+0=9)"],"response_history":["9","0"],"rt":116599,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":863877,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":32179,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":896057,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["7"],"rt":3370,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":899428,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["9"],"rt":2039,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":901468,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":true,"explanation":"it's the number you combine with to get to 0, so subtracted 3 from 9","explanation_history":["it's the number you combine with to get to 0, so subtracted 3 from 9"],"response_history":["6"],"rt":40141,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":941610,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"because you can't use it to make every other number","explanation_history":["because you can't use it to mak e every  other number"],"response_history":["No"],"rt":56951,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":998561,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"because you can't use it to get every other number","explanation_history":["because you can't use it to get every other number"],"response_history":["No"],"rt":20955,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1019518,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"because you can't use it to get every other number","explanation_history":["bec ause you  can't use it to get every other number"],"response_history":["No"],"rt":5630,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1025150,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"because you can't use it to get every other number","explanation_history":["because you can't use it to get every other number"],"response_history":["No"],"rt":5341,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1030492,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answer s can in clude n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":11769,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1042262,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"n-1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["n-1"],"rt":40451,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1082714,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"n-x","explain":true,"explanation":"this is a guess--i'm pretty confused now","explanation_history":["this is a guess--i'm pretty confused j","this is a guess--i'm pretty confused now"],"response_history":["n-x"],"rt":109804,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":1192520,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"i don't know the answer to this","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["i don't know the answer to this"],"rt":27371,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":1219892,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":16041,"trial_type":"q uestion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":1235935,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":2768,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":1238703,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":3311,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":1242016,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14- 0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"True","response":"False","explain":true,"explanation":"i'm just guessing false at this point because i've gotten lost in all of this. i was understanding it at first, then kind of hanging on, now i have no idea","explanation_history":["i'm just gyu","i'm just gy","i'm just guessing false at this point because i've gotten lost in all of this. i was ha","i'm just guessing false at this point because i've gotten lost in all of this. i was h","i'm just guessing false at this point because i've gotten lost in all of this. i was ","i'm just guessing false at this point because i've gotten lost in all of this. i was understanding it at first, then kind of hanging on, nb","i'm just guessing false at this point because i've gotten lost in all of thi s. i was  understanding it at first, then kind of hanging on, now i j","i'm just guessing false at this point because i've gotten lost in all of this. i was understanding it at first, then kind of hanging on, now i have no idea"],"response_history":["False"],"rt":132664,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":1374681,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Never","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Never"],"rt":5927,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":1380610,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, som etimes,  or never? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Sometimes","response":"Never","explain":true,"explanation":"again, so lost now","explanation_history":["again, so lost now"],"response_history":["Never"],"rt":9648,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":1390259,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Never","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Never"],"rt":3839,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":1394100,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about y our back ground. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":2927,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":1397028,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"41","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["41"],"rt":1999,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":1399028,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Some graduate school, no degree","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Some graduate school, no degree"],"rt":4671,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":1403702,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"statistics in college","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["pre-cal","statistics in college"],"rt":20978,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":1424681,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":6495,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":1431176,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":5008,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":1436185,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat ","3 - d efinitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - not at all","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - not at all"],"rt":6112,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":1442298,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3831,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":1446130,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - some what"],"rt":2982,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":1449114,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Female"],"rt":2192,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":1451307,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"english","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["english"],"rt":5026,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":1456334,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"fr ee","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yep","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["yep"],"rt":4920,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":1461255,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"none","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["none"],"rt":4997,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":88,"time_elapsed":1466253,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]